Say you are given n numbers, a1 a2 ….an . With the cost of 1 point you can add or subtract 1 from each number. 
You can apply this operation to the same number any number of times.
Our goal is to make the product of the numbers equal 1.
For example, for n=3 and numbers [1,−3,0] we can make product equal to 1 in 3 points: add 1 to the second element, add 1 to second element again, subtract 1 from third element, so that array becomes [1,−1,−1]. And 1⋅(−1)⋅(−1)=1.
What is the minimum cost we will have to pay to do that?

Input:
The input is an array of integers a1,a2,…,an a1,a2,…,an (−10^9≤ai≤10^9) — the numbers.
Output: 
Output a single number — the minimal number of coins you need to pay to make the product equal to 1.

Test Cases:
input
-1 1
output
2
input
0 0 0 0
output
4
input
-5 -3 5 3 0
output
13
